<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Glimesh Blog</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Glimesh Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 08:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Board Meeting 08/2021</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-08-03-board-meeting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-08-03-board-meeting/</guid><description>Hello everyone, and welcome to the August board meeting for Glimesh. In July we officially hit the one year mark of our original charity stream that we did with Ikaros on July 22nd, and it’s been a very exciting year so far. The future&amp;rsquo;s looking bright, the past two months have been a lot of work and preparation to bring the alpha roadmap forward and I’m excited to share what we’ve been working on with you today.</description></item><item><title>Board Meeting 07/2021</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-07-06-board-meeting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-07-06-board-meeting/</guid><description>Hello everyone and welcome to Glimesh’s first regular board meeting. This meeting will replace our existing weekly team meeting as the primary method of updating our community &amp;amp; the world on Glimesh operations. I hope you enjoy!
Called to order: July 6th, 2021 / 7:00 PM EDT
YouTube Recording You can find a YouTube recording of this video here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Glimcap 19</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-06-16-glimcap-part-nineteen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-06-16-glimcap-part-nineteen/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to Glimcap # 19! This week’s recap includes some news on GCX and some new updates on some of our roadmap items. This week we saw some different than normal metrics that we will be covering as well.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap 18</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-06-08-glimcap-part-eighteen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-06-08-glimcap-part-eighteen/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Glimcap 18&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Welcome to the Glimcap 18. This week we have some big news coming later in June. As usual we are going over the metrics, financials, and wins that we’ve had over the past week. We will have a special announcement at the end of the article so make sure to get all the way to the end.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap 17</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-06-01-glimcap-part-seventeen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-06-01-glimcap-part-seventeen/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to the Glimcap 17. This is the first meeting of June! This week we have some updates on Alpha Phase 2 features, the first 3 months of financials and all your usual metric and win updates.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap 16</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-05-26-glimcap-part-sixteen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-05-26-glimcap-part-sixteen/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to the 16th Glimcap. This week we will be looking at the business in depth, briefly touching on the progress which is being made with Phase 2 Alpha features, and as always rounding up some wins and challenges from the past week.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap 15</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-05-21-glimcap-part-fifteen/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-05-21-glimcap-part-fifteen/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to the 15th Glimcap. We are continually on the grind working at growing the platform and fully developing the features. This week is a small update but a good one as we are seeing some of the fruit of our labors on the marketing side of things.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap 14</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-05-12-glimcap-part-fourteen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-05-12-glimcap-part-fourteen/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome again to our 14th Glimcap! This week we are just covering some of the basic metrics and giving a small update for some of the Phase 2 features. There aren’t a lot of new updates this week but we are showing some renewed growth on some of the socials.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 13</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-05-04-glimcap-part-thirteen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-05-04-glimcap-part-thirteen/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="glimcap-part-13">Glimcap Part 13&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Welcome to week 13 of the Glimcap. This week we have a special update from a member of the team, news from our marketing team, and all the usual metrics and updates to keep you up to date with Glimesh!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 12</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-04-27-glimcap-part-twelve/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-04-27-glimcap-part-twelve/</guid><description>Glimcap Part 12 Welcome to week 12 of the Glimcap. This week we will be showing some of the progress we have been making towards the Alpha Phase 2 features, as well as going through our usual roundups of financials, metrics and wins from the previous week.
Metrics This Week Last Week Diff Discord 5,936 6,012 76⬇ Twitter 9,206 9,208 2⬇ Reddit 584 580 4⬆ Instagram 1,190 1,178 12⬆ Facebook 609 603 6⬆ Users 38,759 38,392 367⬆ MRR $8,160 $8,510 $350⬇ Support Tickets 22 47 25⬇ Last week we covered 2 weeks metrics but this week sees a return to our usual 1 week reporting.</description></item><item><title>What Makes Glimesh Unique?</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-04-26-what-makes-glimesh-unique/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-04-26-what-makes-glimesh-unique/</guid><description>What Makes Glimesh Unique? Here at Glimesh a question we often get asked is ‘Why Glimesh? What makes Glimesh different to the myriad of other platforms out there for streaming?’ Here we will unpack just what it means to choose Glimesh, and hopefully help you understand more about who and what we are.</description></item><item><title>Phase 2 Alpha</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-04-22-phase-2-alpha/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-04-22-phase-2-alpha/</guid><description>Phase 2 Alpha Welcome to the start of Phase 2, first up we should set some expectations! Things will not happen overnight, this will take time as there are many parties which need to coordinate time on a volunteer basis to make all of this happen. Therefore we will not be offering up any deadlines or schedules when it comes to Phase 2, but we do promise to keep you updated on progress each week as well as holding streams and other open approaches such as coding via streams, so you can keep up to date on how things are progressing.</description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 11</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-04-22-the-glimcap-week-eleven/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-04-22-the-glimcap-week-eleven/</guid><description>Glimcap Part 11 Welcome to our 11th Glimcap. Last week we were focused on some exciting news and we cancelled the team meeting in order to focus on Phase 2 of our Alpha Roadmap! This week we have revealed what plans and features we have for the next Phase which you can find in its own blog post here: Phase 2 Alpha Blog and as usual, the Glimcap this week will be covering all the latest goings on with metrics and new platform features.</description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 10</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-04-06-the-glimcap-week-ten/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-04-06-the-glimcap-week-ten/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to the Glimcap Part 10. Last week with the holiday we overlooked publishing the Glimcap (it will be posted with this weeks Glimcap), but we are back and raring to give you all the latest Glimesh happenings with this week&amp;rsquo;s edition of the Glimcap!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Last week marked our official 1 month since launching Glimesh! We have some exciting news coming up about some Roadmap plans, some plans for Growth, and what&amp;rsquo;s in the future for us at Glimesh.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 9</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-03-30-the-glimcap-week-nine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-03-30-the-glimcap-week-nine/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to week 9 of the Glimcap! This week there’s a lot to talk about, from new page designs for mobile, to our new events plan moving forward; we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to share all the news with you this week!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 8</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-03-23-the-glimcap-week-eight/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-03-23-the-glimcap-week-eight/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hello Glimesh! Welcome to week 8 of the Glimcap. This week has been a tough week for growth, and a good week for stability. While we have had some ups and downs, we have a plan of action moving forward, and it’s this plan that we’ll be focusing on this week.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 7</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-03-16-the-glimcap-week-seven/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-03-16-the-glimcap-week-seven/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey everyone, welcome to week 7 of the Glimcap! We have been hard at work this past week optimising and fine tuning the website to continue the hard work from launch week.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This week has seen increased stability across all servers, more new streamers arriving every day, and a continued overwhelming amount of support from everyone.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 6</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-03-09-the-glimcap-week-six/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-03-09-the-glimcap-week-six/</guid><description>&lt;p>So much has been going on at Glimesh and we just can’t keep up with the excitement after launch. Our growth and the support from the GlimFamily has been huge!! This week&amp;rsquo;s Glimcap is a special one as it&amp;rsquo;s our first one since launching the Alpha. We took some time off last week and this week we are hoping to get back into the full swing of things.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This week is going to look a little different from our regular pattern and might continue to look different from here on out.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 5</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-02-23-the-glimcap-week-five/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-02-23-the-glimcap-week-five/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is the first meeting since announcing launch and this week we will be taking you through our top tips to prepare for launch, what we are doing to prepare for launch, and all the latest news about subscriptions!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 4</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-02-18-the-glimcap-week-four/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-02-18-the-glimcap-week-four/</guid><description>&lt;p>This week we’ve made some big announcements regarding launch, edge locations, and a fantastic proof of concept stream last week thanks to members of the GCT and Contributors teams. Continue reading if you want to learn the big LAUNCH NEWS…&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 3</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-02-11-the-glimcap-week-three/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-02-11-the-glimcap-week-three/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to our recap of Tuesday&amp;rsquo;s team meeting from Febraury 9th 2021. We have some exciting news to share in regards to merch, improvements on the site, and a cool new test we performed on the site. There have been some significant developments over this week so keep reading on for more info.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 2</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-02-02-the-glimcap-week-two/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-02-02-the-glimcap-week-two/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to the second weekly Glimesh blog. Our goal is to give you a recap of the Tuesday team meeting for the week. This way if you weren’t able to make it you can still get some of the details of the meeting. We’ve decided to officially name this weekly new recap “The Mesh”. We want to make sure we keep everyone connected to what&amp;rsquo;s going on at Glimesh.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glimcap Part 1</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-01-29-the-glimcap-part-one/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2021-01-29-the-glimcap-part-one/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome Glimesh community to our first weekly recap. This is a new adventure to give you a weekly round up of what’s happening here at Glimesh. We will be overviewing the Tuesday meeting and giving you some other interesting tidbits of news and information that is happening in the community. Our goal will be to put this newsletter out each week on Thursdays and give you the latest Glimesh news.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>December Roadmap &amp; Feature Update</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-12-16-december-roadmap-and-feature-update/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-12-16-december-roadmap-and-feature-update/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hi everyone! We’re not launched yet (sorry) – but we have a ton of new features that are now live on the site, and also a roadmap update for the end of the year!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Security Incident - OAuth Key Exposure</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-11-14-security-incident-oauth-key-exposure/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-11-14-security-incident-oauth-key-exposure/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hello everyone,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On Friday November 13rd 2020 at 11:30 AM EST we were informed of a potential security concern for accessing private developer information. The issue was caused by permissions checks being ignored on the Developer Applications page on our website. This could lead to a situation where you could plainly read another developer applications&amp;rsquo;s oauth client id &amp;amp; client secret. As of 1:14PM EST that same day, the access was prevented and the issue resolved.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Staff Meeting 2020/09/15</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-09-15-staff-meeting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-09-15-staff-meeting/</guid><description/></item><item><title>August Feature Update!</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-08-26-august-feature-update/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-08-26-august-feature-update/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hi everyone! We&amp;rsquo;re not launched yet (sorry) &amp;ndash; but we have a ton of updates that are now live on the site. I wanted to share them with you so you could continue to get a feel for Glimesh and how we&amp;rsquo;ll work once we&amp;rsquo;re launched!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Staff Meeting 2020/08/18</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-08-18-staff-meeting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-08-18-staff-meeting/</guid><description>&lt;p>Regular Glimesh Staff Meeting minutes and documents.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Glimesh Alpha Roadmap</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-08-13-glimesh-alpha-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-08-13-glimesh-alpha-roadmap/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey everyone, happy eve-of-Friday! We&amp;rsquo;ve been super busy over here at Glimesh working on our communication. As we grow, we&amp;rsquo;re understanding the true importance of clearly communicating our goals and objectives as well as providing a single source of truth for any status updates.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Staff Meeting 2020/08/11</title><link>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-08-11-staff-meeting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://blog.glimesh.tv/posts/2020-08-11-staff-meeting/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey everyone! Thanks for visiting our new blog :D. Our first post is all about sharing the results of yesterday&amp;rsquo;s staff meeting. We chatted for about an hour about the Glimesh Roadmap and had some great conversations about how we can communicate effectively and help manage expectations. Thank you all for stopping by either in the DIscord, or watching live on our website!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>